<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfCatagory xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Catagory>
    <Title>Tuition</Title>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>128</R>
      <G>175</G>
      <B>79</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Ratio>0.33333333</Ratio>
    <Explanation>
      Domestic fees apply to Canadian citizens, permanent residents and Convention refugees.
      Costs listed below reflect 100% enrolment (five courses per term).</Explanation>
    <Image>Tuition.png</Image>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <Title>Regular Admisssion Requirments</Title>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>102</R>
      <G>117</G>
      <B>50</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Ratio>0.333333333</Ratio>
    <Explanation>
      Applicants must have a minimum overall average of 65 percent, with no course grade lower than 50 percent, in the following high school courses:

1. ELA 30-1
2. Mathematics 30-1 or Pure Mathematics 30
3. Two of the following: Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Mathematics 31, Physics 30, Computing Science (CSE) Advanced Level Career and Technology Studies (CTS)(minimum 5 credits)
4. An Additional Science, Fine Art, or Humanities 30 Level Course.
    </Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <Title>Previous post-secondary work</Title>
    <Ratio>0.1</Ratio>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>155</R>
      <G>170</G>
      <B>67</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Explanation>
      Admission in this category does not imply or guarantee the transfer of any coursework and/or credential unless a block transfer agreement (internal or external) is in effect and published in the calendar by the Office of the Registrar. In addition, transfer of coursework does not imply or guarantee that an applicant will be admitted.

      Applicants must have successfully completed the following:
      - A minimum of 24 credits of university-transferable coursework, from a recognized institution, with a minimum Admission Grade Point Average (AGPA) of 2.0 on a 4.0 scale.
      - The required core courses listed under the Regular or Mature Admission category.
    </Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <Title>Mature Admisssion Requirments</Title>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>127</R>
      <G>132</G>
      <B>69</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Ratio>0.233333333</Ratio>
    <Explanation>
      Applicants must be 20 years of age or older and have been out of full-time high school at least one year by the beginning of the intake term. Applicants must have a minimum overall average of 60 percent, with no course grade lower than 50 percent, in the following high school courses:
1. ELA 30-1
2. Mathematics 30-1 or Pure Mathematics 30
3. Two of the following: Biology 30, Chemistry 30, Mathematics 31, Physics 30, Computing Science (CSE) Advanced Level Career and Technology Studies (CTS) (minimum 5 credits)
    </Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  
</ArrayOfCatagory>