<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfCatagory xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Catagory>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>188</G>
      <B>64</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Title>Artificial Intelligence</Title>
    <Explanation>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the scientific understanding of the mechanisms underlying thought and intelligent behavior and their embodiment in machines (Association for the Advancement of Artificial Intelligence). Students learn various concepts and applications of AI, such as intelligent agents, knowledge representation, state-space search, expert systems and shells, natural language processing, propositional logic, and learning and cognitive models.</Explanation>
    <Ratio>0.125</Ratio>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>252</R>
      <G>194</G>
      <B>101</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Title>Human-Computer Interaction</Title>
    <Ratio>0.15625</Ratio>
    <Explanation>In human-computer interaction (HCI), students learn the basic components of the interaction design process and programming skills necessary to implement interactive systems. Topics of interest include interface and interaction types, data gathering and analysis to understand and solve design problems, design requirements, prototyping, and usability testing.</Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>229</R>
      <G>147</G>
      <B>3</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Title>Computer Security</Title>
    <Ratio>0.125</Ratio>
    <Explanation>Computer security studies the processes and mechanisms by which computer-based equipment, information and services are protected from unintended or unauthorized access, change or destruction (Wikipedia).</Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>191</R>
      <G>153</G>
      <B>48</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Title>Databases</Title>
    <Ratio>0.156625</Ratio>
    <Explanation>In databases, students study various concepts in data organization and information processing. Topics include database design, normalization theory, transaction management, query processing, and query optimization. Students also learn database support for special data types such as multimedia, spatial data, and XML documents.</Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>165</G>
      <B>0</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Title>Computer Networks</Title>
    <Ratio>0.15625</Ratio>
    <Explanation>In computer networks, students learn the basics of networking, such as network architectures, protocols, client-server programming, security, and network management. They also study a selection of material from multimedia technologies and data compression and decompression.</Explanation>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>187</G>
      <B>0</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Title>Computer Games</Title>
    <Explanation>In computer games, students learn various aspects of computer game design and marketing. It focuses on the history of computer games, computer game markets, evaluation of computer games, creation and testing of interactive narratives, and game interface design. In senior-level courses, students learn modern game engines and programming skills to implement computer games.</Explanation>
    <Ratio>0.15625</Ratio>
  </Catagory>
  <Catagory>
    <TextColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>255</G>
      <B>255</B>
    </TextColor>
    <Title>Parallel Computing</Title>
    <Explanation>Parallel computing is a form of computation in which many calculations are carried out simultaneously, operating on the principle that large problems can often be divided into smaller ones, which are then solved concurrently (Wikipedia). Students learn both the theoretical and practical aspects of parallel computation. Topics of interest include cores, clusters and clouds, and parallel languages and libraries.</Explanation>
    <BackGroundColor>
      <A>255</A>
      <R>255</R>
      <G>140</G>
      <B>0</B>
    </BackGroundColor>
    <Ratio>0.125</Ratio>
  </Catagory>
  <!-- -->
</ArrayOfCatagory>